Guide to the Kenneth S. Pitzer, President of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Kenneth S. Pitzer, president of Stanford University, papers
circa 1968-1970
SC0218
Pitzer, Kenneth S., (Kenneth Sanborn), 1914-1997
28 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
College administrators.; Stanford University--Administration.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Papers, circa 1968-1970
  - Presidents Pitzer's Inauguration - Greetings from other universities and scholarly institutions, 1969 Jun (Box 1)
    - Brown University (Box 1)
    - Buffalo, University of (Box 1)
    - California Institute of Technology (Box 1)
    - California State College at Long Beach (Box 1)
    - California State Polytechnic College (Box 1)
    - California, University of (Box 1)
    - Carnegie Commission (Box 1)
    - Chicago, University of (Box 1)
    - Columbia University (Box 1)
    - Dartmouth College (Box 1)
    - Harvard University (Box 1)
    - Indiana University (Box 1)
    - Institute of International Education (Box 1)
    - Iowa State University (Box 1)
    - Kansas, University of (Box 1)
    - Knox College (Box 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 1)
    - Michigan State University (Box 1)
    - Michigan, University of (Box 1)
    - Minnesota, University of (Box 1)
    - Missouri, University of (Box 1)
    - National Academy of Engineering (Box 2)
    - National Academy of Sciences, U.S.A. (Box 2)
    - Nebraska, University of (Box 2)
    - New York, State University of (Box 2)
    - New York University (Box 2)
    - Northwestern University (Box 2)
    - Ohio State University (Box 2)
    - Oxford, University of (Box 2)
    - Paris, Universite de (Box 2)
    - Pennsylvania State University (Box 2)
    - Pennsylvania, University of (Box 2)
    - Princeton University (Box 2)
    - San Diego State College (Box 2)
    - Santa Clara, University of (Box 2)
    - Syracuse University (Box 2)
    - Texas, University of (Box 2)
    - Toronto, University of (Box 2)
    - Tulane University (Box 2)
    - Utah, University of (Box 2)
    - Vanderbilt University (Box 2)
    - Virginia, University of (Box 2)
    - Washington University (Box 2)
    - Washington State University (Box 2)
    - Washington, University of (Box 2)
    - Yale University (Box 2)
  - Gifts
    - Gifts - A-C, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
    - Gifts - D-G, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
    - Gifts - H-K, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
    - Gifts - J-M, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
    - Gifts - N-R, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
    - Gifts - S, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
    - Gifts - T-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 1A)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Letters re: resignation of Dr. Pitzer (Box 1A)
    - Food Research Institute Building dedication, 1970 Apr 6 (Box 1A)
    - Stanford-in-Britain campus at Cliveden, 1970 Jan 31 (Box 1A)
    - Joseph D. Grant Building for research in clinical sciences, 1969 Jun 20 (Box 1A)
    - William F. Durand and Hugh Hildreth Skilling Building (cancelled), 1969 Jun 9 (Box 1A)
    - Nathan Cummins Art Building dedication, 1969 May 17 (Box 1A)
    - Roscoe Maples Pavilion dedication, 1969 Mar 1 (Box 1A)
    - Dedication of Fraternity Cluster III, 1968 Oct 12 (Box 1A)
    - Stanford associates honor Dr. and Mrs. Sterling at dinner, 1968 Apr 18 (Box 1A)
    - Lowell Berry visit, 1968 Apr 10 (Box 1A)
    - William F. Herrin Hall and William F. Herrin Laboratories dedication, 1967 Nov 30 (Box 1A)
    - Three millionth book presented to Stanford Bender Room, 1967 Nov 7 (Box 1A)
    - Lou Henry Hoover Building dedication Milbank and de Basily Rooms, 1967 Oct 9 (Box 1A)
    - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center dedication, 1967 Sep 9 (Box 1A)
    - Inauguration acceptances (Box 1A)
    - Regrets (Box 1A)
    - Thank you to staff, etc. helping with inauguration (Box 1A)
    - Logistics (Box 1A)
    - Invitations (Box 1A)
    - Congratulations to Dr. Pitzer (Box 1A)
    - Inauguration - committees, meetings, logistics, etc. (Box 1A)
    - Dr. Kenneth S. Pitzer inauguration, 1969 Jun 14 (Box 1A)
  - American Associations of Univeristies
    - AAU (Association of American Universities) and AUBC, 1961-1963 (Box 2A)
    - ACE (American Council on Education), 1961-1965 (Box 2A)
    - ACPRA (American College Public Relations Association), 1966 (Box 2A)
    - Association of Graduate Schools, 1961-1967 (Box 2A)
    - National Commission on Accrediting - AAU (Association of American Universities), 1958-1964 (Box 2A)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1966 (Box 2A)
    - American Association of Univerity Professors, 1964 (Box 2A)
    - AID (Agency for International Development), 1962 (Box 2A)
    - Association des universités partiellement ou entièrement de langue française, 1961 (Box 2A)
    - Tulane Civil Rights Case, 1962 (Box 2A)
    - Committee on University and World Affairs, 1962 (Box 2A)
    - West German Rectors' conference, 1961-1965 (Box 2A)
    - Rights and Responsibilites of Universities Conference - Tokyo, 1962-1965 (Box 2A)
    - Associaton of American Universities International conference - Tokyo, 1965 (Box 2A)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officer Training Corps), 1961-1965 (Box 2A)
    - Committee on larger responsibilities (Box 2A)
    - The economics of faculty salaries, 1966 (Box 2A)
    - Special Committee - Growing Pressures in Graduate Work, 1960 (Box 2A)
    - AAU (Assoication of American Universities) - Publicity, 1965 (Box 2A)
    - Post doctoral fellow problem, 1960-1963 (Box 2A)
    - AAU (Assoication of American Universities) Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 2A)
    - AAU (Assoication of American Universities) Minutes, 1960-1967 (Box 2A)
  - General
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) constitution, 1967-1968 (Box 3A)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) cultural affairs committee, 1967 Nov 1 (Box 3A)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) legislature summer committee on the judiciary, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Ad Hoc Social Regulation Committee, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) special programs, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) student research and project center (Box 3A)
    - Association of Hungarian Students in North America Inc., 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Athenian School (opening September 1965), 1965-1967 (Box 3A)
    - AAWU (Athletic Association of Western Universities) financial aid-academic standings, work program, 1964-1967 (Box 3A)
    - The Atlantic Monthly, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Bay Area Student Association, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - British education, 1968 (Box 3A)
    - Brown, Mr. Ralph J., 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Brucker, Herbert - emeritus editor of the Hartford Courant, 1966-1968 (Box 3A)
    - California legislature senate fact finding committee on education, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - California non-partisan voter registration committee, inc., 1966 (Box 3A)
    - California State committee on public education, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - California State department of education, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Campus coordinating committee, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Campus report, 1968-1969 (Box 3A)
    - Centre national, 1964-1965 (Box 3A)
    - Channing House, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Citizens national committee on higher education, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Civil action day committee (Box 3A)
    - King death-letters, 1968 (Box 3A)
    - Pacific Eight - miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 3A)
    - Pacific Eight - women's athletics, 1964-1970 (Box 3A)
    - Pacific Eight - conference, 1966-1968 (Box 3A)
    - Pacific Eight - articles of association, by-laws, 1958-1964 (Box 3A)
    - Stanford cabinet, 1968-1969 (Box 3A)
    - California State chamber of commerce, 1962-1967 (Box 3A)
    - California College and University Faculty Association, 1968 (Box 3A)
    - California Department of Motor Vehicles, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - California Department of Public Health (Box 3A)
    - California Directory of Institutions of Higher Learning, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Class rankings - practice discontinued, 1967 Sep 1 (Box 3A)
    - Clubhouse, 1959-1967 (Box 3A)
    - Coldwell, Banker and Company - manager, shopping center (Box 3A)
    - Stanford Committee For a Free University, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Committee for an Effective and Durable Peace in Asia, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities, 1968 (Box 3A)
    - Committee for Non-Violent Action - West, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Committee for Research on the Development of International Institutions, 1965-1966 (Box 3A)
    - Committee of responsibility, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Computer date-matching program, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - CONSCIENCE (Committee on National Student Citizenship in Every National Case of Emergency), 1965 (Box 3A)
    - California-Stanford Consortium for International Programs, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Coordinating Council on Education for the Disadvantaged, 1965-1966 (Box 3A)
    - Christian De Guigne/Stauffer Chemical Company, 1966-1967 (Box 3A)
    - Eating facilities/staff, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Economic Opportunity Commission of Santa Clara County, 1965-1966 (Box 3A)
    - Ecumenical Colloquium (Stanford and Santa Clara Universities), 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1965-1967 (Box 3A)
    - Educational Opportunity Bank, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Far West Labroatory for Education Research and Development, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Farm Workers (attempt to organize) (Grape Boycott), 1965-1969 (Box 3A)
    - Federal Judicial Procedures Center (Box 3A)
    - Financial aids - other institutions, 1963 (Box 3A)
    - Foothill Expressway, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Freshman convocation, 1968-1969 (Box 3A)
    - Freshman English, 1966-1967 (Box 3A)
    - Goodan, Mrs. Roger, 1961-1964 (Box 3A)
    - Grades and grading - general information (Box 3A)
    - Graduate reception, 1965-1969 (Box 3A)
    - Graduate reception, 1966-1968 (Box 3A)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Guide Service/Drivers (Box 3A)
    - Health Reports (Box 3A)
    - Hispanic American studies, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Hobson, Jesse E., 1955-1961 (Box 3A)
    - Holladay House, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Homecoming, 1964-1966 (Box 3A)
    - Hoover fireplace, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Inaugurations - general information, 1965-1966 (Box 3A)
    - India Council of the Asia Society, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Institute for College and University Administrators (Box 3A)
    - International Executive Service Corps, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - International Programs of American Universities, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - International Science Foundation, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - International student fund, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Interstate Compact on Education, 1965 (Box 3A)
    - Lindsay, Frank, 1957-1968 (Box 3A)
    - Lomita Hall, 1967 (Box 3A)
    - Mental Retardation Center, 1965-1967 (Box 3A)
    - Miscellaneous organizations, 1958 (Box 3A)
    - National Opinion Research Center, 1961-1966 (Box 3A)
    - National Teachers Corporation, 1966 (Box 3A)
    - Richard M. Nixon/President Nixon communications, 1960-1970 (Box 3A)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organizations, 1965-1968 (Box 3A)
  - Stanford Research Institute
    - Commission to poll Stanford faculty and students on the issue of SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - Stanford Relationship, 1969 (Box 4A)
    - European long range planning service client conference Zurich, 1968 Jan 29-30 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - San Francisco, 1968 Dec 5 (Box 4A)
    - Financial statements, 1960-1967 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - International Committee (Auxiliary) (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - Executive Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - policy re: fund raising (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - North Atlantic Industrial Conference, 1967 Oct 26 (Box 4A)
    - Pacific Industrial Conference - Australia, 1967 Apr (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - minutes and reports, 1965-1966 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1965-1966 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - annual meeting general members, 1963-1965 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - Japanese Advisory Council, 1962-1963 (Box 4A)
    - Financial Committee (Box 4A)
    - Joint committee of Stanford University and SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1967-1968 (Box 4A)
    - Liaison committee (Box 4A)
    - Membership committee (Box 4A)
    - Personnel committee (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - Advisory Councils, 1961-1962 (Box 4A)
    - Sibbott, Morgan (Box 4A)
    - McBean, Athall (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - Director (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1966-1967 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1962-1963, 1964-1965 (Box 4A)
    - Committee to study SRI (Stanford Research Institute) and Stanford relationship, 1965-1966 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) board of directors, 1966-1967 (Box 4A)
    - Stanford Research Institute (SRI) board of directors, 1965-1966 (Box 4A)
    - Speical committee of SRI (Stanford Research Institute) board of directors, 1965 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) Board of Directors, 1963-1964 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1963 (Box 4A)
    - Miscellaneous Minutes, Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1961-1962 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute), 1960-1961 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) Board of Directors Meeting LVA., 1961 Oct 6 (Box 4A)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) Board of Directors, 1961 Sep 1 (Box 4A)
    - Miscellaneous copies of SRI (Stanford Research Institute) Journal (Box 4A)
  - Confidential
    - Anton, Anatol (record of activites at Stanford), 1963-1967 (Box 5A)
    - Baran, Professor Paul (Economics), 1954-1965 (Box 5A)
    - Baran letters, 1962 (Box 5A)
    - Confidential - general files, 1954-1955 (Box 5A)
    - Confidential, 1955-1968 (Box 5A)
    - Dismissal Cases (Box 5A)
    - Lucille Allen, Dean of Women - resignation, 1965 Feb (Box 5A)
    - Grant-Fund for the Republic Law School $25,000, Testimony, Communism (Box 5A)
    - Fund For The Republic - clippings, etc. (Box 5A)
    - Fund For The Republic Industrial Corporation and Labor Unions, 1957 (Box 5A)
    - Ex-communist witnesses and their interrogators (Box 5A)
    - Fund For The Republic - Herbert L. Packer (Box 5A)
    - A tale of two typewriters (Fund for the Republic) Herbert L. Packer (Box 5A)
    - Grant-Fund for the Republic, Inc. Law Review, Civil Liberties, summer, 1965 (Box 5A)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1955 (Box 5A)
    - Gantner, Vallejo - mental case, 1954-1964 (Box 5A)
    - Hatfield, Ronald (Box 5A)
    - Hourani, Gihaleb (Box 5A)
    - Nohrnberg, Agnes (Box 5A)
    - Professor Fayez Sayegh - political science (Box 5A)
    - Dr. Sterling's file - SLAC (Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program) Physics department relations, 1961-1963 (Box 5A)
    - Student discipline, suspension and the Frank Morse case (Box 5A)
    - Students - special cases (Box 5A)
    - Unique, 1959-1962 (Box 5A)
  - Subject files
    - A-general (Box 1B)
    - Academic Plant, 1964-1966 (Box 1B)
    - Accreditation miscellanous correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Activism (at Stanford), 1965 Aug-1968 (Box 1B)
    - Activism - other campuses, 1965 Apr-1968 Aug (Box 1B)
    - Administrative organization, 1954-1966 (Box 1B)
    - Administrative search, 1968 Jun 31-1970 Aug (Box 1B)
    - Advance Newsletter of the Southwest Center for Advanced Studies (Box 1B)
    - Advisors, 1968-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Affiliations with other universities (proposals), 1965-1970 (Box 1B)
    - AID (Agency for International Development), 1963-1968 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni (general), 1967 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni assembly, 1969 May 22-24 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni Association - including background material, 1966-1968 Aug (Box 1B)
    - Alumni Association Executive Board and Advisory Council (including minutes of meetings), 1965-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni calls reunions, 1967-1970 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni Association and Stanford In Particular, 1962-1967 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni awards, honors and special services, 1966-1967 (Box 1B)
    - Stanford alumni clubs, 1968-1970 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni club - Hawaii, 1961-1968 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni club of Los Angeles, 1961-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni association - Stanford Nurses Club, 1961 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni of Portland and Seattle, 1967 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni Directory, 1959-1968 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni Review (Box 1B)
    - Stanford Medical Alumni Association, 1966-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni Herbert Hoover Gold Medal, 1962-1970 (Box 1B)
    - Alumni conferences - general data, 1964 (Box 1B)
    - Amateur Athletic Union of the United States, 1963-1964 (Box 1B)
    - America-Great Britian relationship (Box 1B)
    - American Academy In Rome and Athens, 1961-1966 (Box 1B)
    - The American Assembly, 1966-1968 (Box 1B)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 1B)
    - American Association of University Women, 1966-1970 (Box 1B)
    - American Colleges Public Relations Association, 1967 (Box 1B)
    - ACE (American Council on Education), 1968-1969 (Box 1B)
    - ACE (American Council on Education) an internship program for fellows in academic administration), 1965-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs Publications American Council on Education, 1969-1970 (Box 1B)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs, American Council on Education, 1968-1969 (Box 1B)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1968-1969 (Box 1B)
    - Americans For Reappraisal of Far Eastern Policy, 1965 (Box 1B)
    - American Institute For Research, 1965-1967 (Box 1B)
    - American Judicature Society, 1967 (Box 1B)
    - American Physical Society, 1966 (Box 1B)
    - American Society for Technion, 1961-1968 (Box 1B)
    - The American Student, 1966 (Box 1B)
    - American Universities Field Staff, 1964-1965 (Box 1B)
    - Amigos Anonymous, 1965-1967 (Box 1B)
    - Applications (teachings ), 1969-1970 (Box 1B)
    - Applications (not defined) (Box 1B)
    - American Red Cross, 1956-1958 (Box 2B)
    - American Schools of Oriental Research (Box 2B)
    - Annual reports, 1967-1970 (Box 2B)
    - A3M (April III Movement)/Statements, 1969 (Box 2B)
      - See: Free Campus Movement For Suit Against the University For Lack of Protection From Radicals Harassment Continues At Applied Electronics Laboratories Trustees Hearing on Standford Research Institute (SRI), 1969 Apr 30 (Box 2B)
      - Stanford Judicial Council takes jurisdiction over disciplinary matters following AEL disruption (Box 2B)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) (Box 2B)
      - Hoover Institution Demonstration - A3M (April III Movement) (Box 2B)
    - Government Intervenes-see McClellan committee file (Box 2B)
    - S.R.I. - Hanover Harassment (Box 2B)
      - AEL (Applied Electronics Laboratory) Disruption, 1969 April 9 (Box 2B)
      - A3M (April III Movement) - efforts to raise funds to cover legal defenses (Box 2B)
    - A3M (April III Movement) - use of facilities (Box 2B)
    - A3M (April III Movement) - after Encina (Box 2B)
      - Copies of important resolutions news releases and newspaper articles re: A3M (April III Movement) (Box 2B)
      - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - prosecution (Box 2B)
      - A3M (April III Movement) - Related to SRI-Stanford Relations - classified research (Box 2B)
      - Pitzer/Administration Statements A3M (April III Movement) Encina Disruption, 1969 May 1 (Box 2B)
    - Arboretum, 1968 (Box 2B)
    - Association of Graduate Schools Dean Steere, 1957-1967 (Box 2B)
    - ARA (Associates Radio Astronomy), 1966-1967 (Box 2B)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) - constitution, 1969 (Box 2B)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) Academic Affairs Committee - to strengthen advising program, 1968 (Box 2B)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University), Advisory Board to the, 1968-1969 (Box 2B)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University) President, Patrick C. Shea, 1970-1971 (Box 2B)
    - ASSU (Associated Students of Stanford University), 1967 (Box 2B)
    - AAU (Association of American Universities), 1964-1969 Feb (Box 2B)
    - AICCU (Association of Independent California Colleges and Universities), 1965-1969 Jul (Box 2B)
    - Associations, Miscellaneous Stanford - member or requested to join, 1965-1967 (Box 2B)
    - B, 1966 Mar-1969 Aug (Box 2B)
    - Bechtel International Center, 1964-1969 Aug (Box 2B)
    - Black Power/activism, 1966-1968 (Box 2B)
    - Black Arts Theatre, 1968 (Box 2B)
    - Black Student Union, 1968-1969 (Box 2B)
      - Black Student Union demands made, 1968 Feb 4 (Box 2B)
      - Black Power attack on Payton Jordan in connection with role as coach on U.S. Olympic track team (Box 2B)
    - Overseas book project, 1965-1967 (Box 2B)
    - Bookstore, 1966-1970 (Box 2B)
    - Boys' Clubs of America, 1967 (Box 2B)
    - Budget, 1968-1970 (Box 2B)
      - Student involvement in budgetary affairs (Box 2B)
    - C, 1965-1970 (Box 2B)
    - California Community Colleges, 1968-1969 (Box 2B)
    - California Legislature/Legislation, 1969-1970 (Box 2B)
    - Joint Committee on Higher Education Califonia Legislature, 1969 (Box 2B)
    - Campus report, 1969-1970 (Box 2B)
    - Otis Chandler, 1961-1970 (Box 2B)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1966-1970 (Box 3B)
    - Coeducational Cooperative (Box 3B)
    - Columbia University (Box 3B)
    - Commencement, 1969 (Box 3B)
    - Commencement, 1970 (Box 3B)
    - Complaint and commendation list and handling information, 1966-1968 (Box 3B)
    - Complaint lists from General Secretaries office, 1968-1970 (Box 3B)
    - Concerned groups, 1966-1969 (Box 3B)
    - Condolence letters, 1969-1970 Aug (Box 3B)
    - Conferences - off campus (Box 3B)
      - World Conference on the Role of the Quest for Peace, 1968 (Box 3B)
      - Science and Technology Symposium - Pitzer participated, 1970 Mar 8 (Box 3B)
    - Conferences - on campus, 1969-1970 (Box 3B)
      - Cubberley Conference, 1966 (Box 3B)
      - SES/ASSU Asilomar Conference, 1970 Jan 23-24 (Box 3B)
      - 1970 Stanford Campus Conference, The University and Society: Education For What? (Box 3B)
      - Conferences - Model United Nations, 1956-67 (Box 3B)
      - Conference on Peaceful Change in Modern Society, 1969 Nov 18-20 (Box 3B)
      - Population Biology Conference (Memorial Auditorium 8:30am), 1969 Oct 18 (Box 3B)
      - Technology and the Third World (student sponsored conference), 1969 Oct 18 (Box 3B)
      - Leadership Conference, 1968 Sep 27 (Box 3B)
    - Conferences miscellaneous, 1960-1969 (Box 3B)
    - Congratulations and best wishes, 1968-1970 (Box 3B)
    - Co-ops (off campus living), 1966 (Box 3B)
    - Daily, The Stanford, 1966-1969 Aug (Box 3B)
    - Directory (Stanford University Bawl Out) (Box 3B)
    - DOW Chemical Company Recruiting, 1967-1968 (Box 3B)
    - Drugs, 1966-1968 (Box 3B)
    - Drugs (LSD in particular) (Box 3B)
    - Eating Clubs Inc. Inter Club Council, 1963-1968 (Box 3B)
    - Educational Digest, 1969 Sep-1970 Jul (Box 3B)
  - Education and World Affairs-Invitations
    - Education and World Affairs, 1963-1969 Feb (Box 4B)
    - Education Digest, 1968 Oct-1969 Jul (Box 4B)
    - Exchange programs, 1954-1968 Oct (Box 4B)
    - Faculty awards - honors and prizes, 1968-1970 (Box 4B)
    - Fall out Shelter, 1963-1968 (Box 4B)